Once you rolled out your pie crust take a spatula and just kind of work it under it cause you don't want to tear it.
If it's stuck anywhere from underneath non commercial surface and it would be hard to get off.
So obviously I can't go all the way to the middle but to move it to our pie pan.
We're just going to flop it this over anyway like a burrito.
So now we can get to the middle and we can roll it again this just makes it easier to transfer to our 8" pie pan.
Then transfer it and roll it gently back out, the really good part about making pie crust is that pie crust taste really good raw, and you always have little scrap pieces like this you can eat.
So take advantage of that don't let your kids see you do that, my grandmother use to say you get worms if you do that.
Anyway and there you go you just trim it and decorate it and then your ready to put your pie filling in.
To trim the edges you just take a regular pairing knife and just that really just works good if you go like that and it comes off just dandy.
Place it like this then it's not quite high enough just go ahead and take a little scrap piece and push it back in there.
It's really easy to add and take away pieces for one area into the other area just fine, and once you done that just go ahead and trim it off like such.